It's time to put all of these data engineering skills to use.
到了把所学的数据工程技术学以致用的时候了
You have a really cool project ahead of you.
等待你的是一个非常酷的项目
Our partners at Figure Eight are providing
我们的合作伙伴 Figure 8 提供了
pre-labeled tweets and text messages from real life disasters.
预先标记好的、在灾害发生时发出的推特和短信消息
Your task is to repair this data with an ETL Pipeline
你的任务是使用 ETL 管道来处理这些数据
and then use a Machine Learning Pipeline to build a supervised learning model.
然后使用机器学习管道来搭建一个监督学习模型
Before you start, Robert is going to give us some background on where
在开始之前 Robert 会介绍一下数据集的来源
the dataset came from and how Figure Eight prepared the data for us.
以及 Figure 8 是如何准备这份数据的
Thank you. So, this is one of the most important problems that
谢谢 这是我们目前试图用数据科学和机器学习
we're trying to solve in Data Science and Machine Learning right now.
解决的最重要的问题之一
So following a disaster,
在灾害之后
typically you will get millions and millions of communications
通常 当时你会得到很多消息
either direct or via social media right at the time
无论是通过短信或是社交媒体
when disaster response organizations have
这个时候是灾害应对组织
the least capacity to filter and then pull out the messages which are the most important.
过滤消息 提取关键信息能力最弱的时候
Often it really is only one in
通常 每一千条消息中
every thousand messages that might be relevant to the disaster response professionals.
只有一条可能会和灾害应对措施相关
So, the way that disasters are typically responded to,
所以 灾害应对组织通常的做法是
is that different organizations will take care of different parts of the problem.
让不同的组织处理不同的问题
So one organization will care about water,
比如 一个组织关心供水情况
another will care about blocked roads,
另一个组织关心道路阻塞情况
another will care about medical supplies.
另一个组织关心医疗保障情况
So, when you look at the data,
所以在你查看数据的时候
you'll see that these are
你会发现数据带有类别标签
the categories that we have pulled out for each of these datasets.
因为是从不同的数据集中提取的
So, we actually used Figure Eight for many of
其实 我们使用 Figure 8 提取
the disasters from which these messages are taken
不同灾害数据集中的消息
then combined these datasets and relabeled them so that
然后将它们结合起来 重新标记
they're consistent labels across the different disasters,
让各种灾害的分类标记都是一致的
and this is to allow you to investigate the different trends that you
让你可以能够探索发现各种趋势
might be able to find and to build supervised Machine Learning models.
并搭建监督机器学习模型
So you'll see for example,
你会发现 比如
when you look at a keyword like water,
你想关注 水 这个关键词
that's actually a very small percent of the time that,
其实这个词只有很少的时候
that will map to someone who needs
会出现在极度缺水的人发的消息里
fresh drinking water and also that will miss people who say they're thirsty,
而且还会漏掉那些很需要水
but don't use the word, "Water."
但是没有用到 水 这个词的人
So, supervised Machine Learning-based approaches are going
这样看来 基于监督机器学习的方法
to be a lot more accurate than anyone could do with keyword searching,
会比关键词搜索能做到的准确得多
but this is actually a big gap right now in disaster response contexts.
但是目前在灾害处理方面这些问题还没有完全解决
So, I really look forward to seeing what you build in your projects and hopefully
所以 我非常期待看到你的项目
discover new trends and new ways of building
希望你发现新的趋势和
Machine Learning models that can help us respond to future disasters.
搭建机器学习模型的新方法 以帮助我们应对未来的灾害
One of my favorite parts about this project is how meaningful the work is.
我们喜欢这个项目的原因就是它的现实意义
Think about the benefits this solution brings to
想想这个解决方案能够带给那些
people affected by natural disasters around the world.
受到灾害影响人们的帮助
In the next section,
在下一章节
you'll find more instructions on how to complete the project,
你会看到如何完成该项目的更多指导
including an overview of the provided code and a rubric.
包括我们提供的代码的介绍和一份审阅标准
Good luck with your projects and I look forward to seeing the results.
祝你好运 期待看到你的结果